[
  {
    "domain": "Anatomie",
    "subdomain": "Syst\u00e8me osseux",
    "subsystem": "Cr\u00e2ne",
    "type": "R\u00e9ponse courte",
    "question": "test",
    "correct_answer": "Vrai",
    "explanation": "Aucune explication fournie."
  },
  {
    "domain": "Anatomie",
    "subdomain": "Syst\u00e8me osseux",
    "subsystem": "Cr\u00e2ne",
    "type": "QCM",
    "question": "fee",
    "options": [
      "Premi\u00e8re option",
      "",
      "",
      "test"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Premi\u00e8re option",
    "explanation": "Aucune explication fournie."
  },
  {
    "domain": "Anatomie",
    "subdomain": "Syst\u00e8me respiratoire",
    "subsystem": "Poumons",
    "type": "QCM",
    "question": "Question placeholder",
    "options": [
      "Option 1",
      "Option 2",
      "Option 3",
      "Option 4"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Option 1",
    "explanation": "Ceci est une question placeholder."
  },
  {
    "domain": "Anatomie",
    "subdomain": "Syst\u00e8me circulatoire",
    "subsystem": "Vaisseaux sanguins",
    "type": "QCM",
    "question": "Test",
    "options": [
      "Premi\u00e8re option",
      "",
      "",
      "test"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Premi\u00e8re option",
    "explanation": "Aucune explication fournie."
  },
  {
    "domain": "Anatomie",
    "subdomain": "Syst\u00e8me circulatoire",
    "subsystem": "C\u0153ur",
    "type": "QCM",
    "question": "test",
    "options": [
      "Premi\u00e8re option",
      "",
      "",
      "test"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Premi\u00e8re option",
    "explanation": "Aucune explication fournie."
  },
  {
    "domain": "Anatomie",
    "subdomain": "Syst\u00e8me circulatoire",
    "subsystem": "C\u0153ur",
    "type": "R\u00e9ponse courte",
    "question": "test",
    "correct_answer": "test",
    "explanation": "Aucune explication fournie."
  },
  {
    "domain": "Anatomie",
    "subdomain": "Syst\u00e8me circulatoire",
    "subsystem": "C\u0153ur",
    "type": "Vrai/Faux",
    "question": "test",
    "options": [
      "Vrai",
      "Faux"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Vrai",
    "explanation": "Aucune explication fournie."
  },
  {
    "domain": "Anatomie",
    "subdomain": "Syst\u00e8me osseux",
    "subsystem": "Cr\u00e2ne",
    "type": "QCM",
    "question": "",
    "options": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correct_answer": "",
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "domain": "Anatomie",
    "subdomain": "Syst\u00e8me osseux",
    "subsystem": "Cr\u00e2ne",
    "type": "QCM",
    "question": "",
    "options": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correct_answer": "",
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "domain": "Anatomie",
    "subdomain": "Syst\u00e8me circulatoire",
    "subsystem": "C\u0153ur",
    "type": "Vrai/Faux",
    "question": "",
    "options": null,
    "correct_answer": "Vrai",
    "explanation": ""
  }
]